

CONTACT

**** +971 50 7372944

Djafridjanette26@gmail.com

Al Barsha, Dubai

EDUCATION

Bachelors – Economy Management – Algeria October 2015 – 2016

Higher Institute of Management ISM – Algeria Web Development (BTS) + Marketing September 2016 – 2018

High School – Chemmam Amar -Algeria September 2013 – June 2015

LANGUAGES

FRENCH ARABIC ENGLISH

DJANETTE DJAFRI

Property Sales Consultant

PROFILE SUMMARY

I describe myself as being highly organized, as well as possessing strong, interpersonal communication skills. I have acquire abilities to deal with people at all levels, and take independent decisions in high-pressure environment. My qualifications and experience enables me to plan new techniques and procedures quickly, I am self starter with a high level of motivation towards acceptance and progression I have attained success for over five years in the field of sales and customer service. I am ready for a long term association where my acquired skills and knowledge can make a substantial contribution to accompanies objective and bottom line of profitability.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Property Consultant

First Group, Dubai 2022-2023

- 1. Market Knowledge: Stay updated on market trends, local developments, and competitor projects to provide accurate information and insights to potential buyers.
- 2. Product Understanding: Thoroughly understand the off-plan property, including its features, amenities, floor plans, and payment structures, to effectively communicate its value to potential buyers.
- 3.Lead Generation: Actively generate leads through networking, referrals, online marketing, instagram reel and other channels to maintain a healthy pipeline of potential buyers
- 4.Client Relationships: Build and maintain strong relationships with clients by providing exceptional customer service, promptly addressing inquiries, and guiding them through the purchasing process
- 5. Negotiation: Skillfully negotiate terms, pricing, and payment plans with potential buyers while balancing the interests of both the developer and the buyer.

Portfolio Manager OG Hills Real Estate, Dubai

Jan 2021 to 2022

- Conducting property market analysis to advise clients on potential investments
- Building and maintaining relationships with property owners and clients
- Assisting clients in property transactions, negotiations, and legalities
- Staying informed about local real estate regulations and market trends for effective client guidance.

Telesales Jan 2020 - 2021

Al Wissam Property - Algiers, Algeria

- 1. Make outgoing calls to customers to advise them of products and services that may be of interest to them. Take customer information- Lead generation through cold calling and follow-ups
- 2.- Conducting property presentations over the phone
- 3.- Handling client inquiries and providing detailed information
- 4.- Nurturing leads through consistent communication
- 5.- Closing deals through effective persuasion and negotiation. and update it in the database as required. Put through relevant sales and contracts for sales of goods or services.